kollywoodzone.com 2018-03-22

# Kollywood Zone Privacy Policy

**Information Automatically Logged**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. The IP is simply stored for security purposes, such as a DOS attack. Your IP is not used for any other purposes. 

**Advertisers**

We use third-party advertising companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and cookies received with banner ads are used only for the purpose of serving the relevant ads. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about Google's use of the DART cookie and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Cookies**

We store a small text file called a cookie on your computer to track session data and persist your login (if needed) for your convenience. A session cookie expires when you exit your browser. A persistent cookie stays on your computer until it is deleted. You can remove persistent cookies by following the directions provided in your browser's "help" files.

**Personal Information**

This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. However, at times, we may run certain advertising offer for which filling out a survey is required. This information may be used to target our advertisements. Individual responses are not kept on file, and none of this information is sold to anyone outside the site 

At no time is personal information collected without explicit consent 

We may provide features exclusively to our members(in future). Our registration process requires you to provide KollywoodZone with a valid email address as well as a username. Optional information such as your first and last name, year of birth, zip code, and country of residence helps KollywoodZone have a better understanding of its visitors and members. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of special features offered only to our members.

**Surveys and Contests**

We may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on KollywoodZone.com. If you participate we will request certain Personal Information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code).  
We only use this information internally to determine eligibility, notify contest winners, and to measure the success of our efforts.

**Minor's Privacy**

We do not collect or maintain information from those people we actually know are under 13 years old, and no part of this site is structured to attract anyone under 13 years old.

**Contact us:**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us by sending an email to [admin@kollywoodzone.com](mailto:admin@kollywoodzone.com) or by filling the contact form. 

**This privacy policy is subject to change and we advise you to review it periodically**
